The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Twenty-First Episode
The Magic Cookies
It's time to wake up
Prince Sapphire.
Prince Sapphire!
It's time to get up!
Good heavens!
Prince, it is time to go to the
secret room for your lessons!
Yes, Garigori, I know!
I will be back soon!
No, Sapphire! You must
study at least until nine o'clock!
You are very late
this morning, Sapphire.
Put this dress on right
away. I will help you. There!
Is this the dress that my
mother had prepared for me?
Yes, it is. You must take
cooking and sewing lessons...
...to be able to become as
good as your dear mother.
Alright, I will take the lessons.
But I can't go horseback
riding in this dress!
You would appreciate it more if
you behaved more like a woman.
- Let me help you!
- No, I don't want to!
- Come on!
- I want to do it myself!
How pretty you are...
Now, to start,
slice this bread.
I can't do it! I don't know how!
If you warm up the knife, you'll
be able to slice it more easily.
Like this, look! Like this!
- Chop! Chop! Chop!
- I understand.
I don't know how to do it!
I don't know how to cut it well!
Don't you have a knife
that's a bit longer?
See if you can do better
with this.
- Good! This one works!
- Be careful not to cut yourself.
- It's very sharp.
- Really?
My God, Princess!
What do you want to do?!
Sapphire!
Great! This cuts much better!
But when you cook,
you must use the right tools
- All right...
- Good morning, everyone
- Good morning, Your Majesty!
- Did you sleep well?
But tell me:
who is that girl?
Good heavens!
But you really are Sapphire!
Yes! Here is breakfast!
You are really very good.
Here you go, father!
And you are served too, mother!
You really are
a beautiful and good girl!
I can do everything,
if I only try.
What's wrong? What's happening?
Why are you shouting?
Nothing, nothing...
Don't worry.
How messy you are!
I had arranged them so well!
Yes, I'm sorry... Do you want to spread
the tablecloth now?
What?... Ah, this one!
I am so sorry, father.
Yes, I forgive you, but
hurry up, please, Sapphire!
All things considered, it would have been
better if you were born a boy, you know?
Why so early?
Well, I wanted to tell you that...
- Really?!
- Yes, sir!
This is the pastry!
Stand up straight!
Do a somersault! Bark!
I put the medicine in
it that forces people...
..to obey any order!
Good! Have many pastries made immediately!
And make sure the King, the
Queen and Sapphire eat them today,
during afternoon tea,
together with the other pastries!
Splendid!
Really good!
Why did you eat
my pastry?
The pastries force people
to obey any order.
Where are you going, damn parrot?
I ate it! I ate it!
It's time you dressed again
as a boy.
Ah, finally! Right away!
Here I am!
We wanted to raise her
as a boy...
...and now she's a tomboy!
Hey, parrot! Halt!
Strange, it stopped all of a sudden!
Now come onto my hand.
This must be
Nylon's parrot.
Hey, my parrot!
My little parrot!
- Oh, Prince!
- Is it yours? I'll give it back to you right away.
It doesn't matter,
I'll take it back later.
Now I have to take
a long walk! Long!
How strange...! There's something
wrong with this parrot.
Listen, tell me everything you know
- If you eat those pastries...
- What happens?
- Have some pastries made!
- Make some pastries?
But what pastries
are you talking about?!
Duralumin! This parrot
talked about pastries...
...that force people
to obey any order!
Pastries that force you
to obey orders?!
What the hell is this about?!
Nylon, do you know anything about this?
I don't know anything about
it. What are you talking about?
You're lying! A moment
ago it seemed like you knew!
But what the hell is happening to you?
It seems like you had
a horrible dream!
I'm sure they will use
those pastries...
..for some conspiracy of theirs
The pastries will surely be made
in some pastry shop.
I'll manage to find it.
You are Prince Sapphire, right?
- Where are you going?
- There's a pastry shop.
...in the woods!
I'm going to see it!
We are also going to the woods
to see it!
The walls are made
of sponge cake!
The snow on the roof is whipped cream!
The pebbles made of popcorn
are delicious!
- Delicious!
- What a beautiful, delicious place!
Hey, you!
Go away, you damn kids
I have to make some pastries
that were ordered,
so get out of my way
and let me work in peace!
Ordered... Just as I thought! It's
likely they are having them made here.
Opal, go to the castle and bring me
my girl's dress right away.
This will do!
You, Opal, wait for me here
Who is disturbing me?
I'm busy, for heaven's sake!
Are you a customer?
No, I want to work.
I heard that the pastry chef...
...needed someone to
help him with his work.
So, can you let
me work with you?
Today I have so much
to do that I'll take you on.
How kind!
Do you make pastries
in such a small room?
No! Do you perhaps think I can
make pastries inside pastries? Come!
Good heavens! There's
a room underground!
What a great place
to work! It's fantastic!
Of course, since I am the
best pastry chef in the world!
Hey, you!
yes?
Go and light the fire
in that oven, over there!
- Come on!
- Yes!
Well, lighting a fire
is super easy.
Good heavens!
Hey! Don't you even know how to
light a fire?!
I'm sorry,
but this wood is wet!
You've turned...
black as coal...
...even the pastry dough! It's ruined!
Then we won't be able to
make the pastries anymore!
Oh, yes! I will make them at all costs!
Before tea time!
You clean everything up!
Yes!
Now I'll put in the medicine
that I was ordered to.
Now come here to help me
Take a nice handful of dough
and shape the pastry.
Afterward, I will put it in the oven.
Like this.
My God, it's too big!
But how misshapen mine are!
There's no need for you to make
any more. Put mine in the oven.
Yes!
I've got it! I will mess up on purpose
and drop all the pastries!
Stupid! Why don't you
try to be more careful?
I'm so sorry, Mr. Pastry Chef!
How come you aren't capable
of doing such a simple job?
Even a child could do it!
Can't you be less distracted?
Hey, boss!
Boss, did you make the pastries?
I'm baking them right
now! Just wait a moment.
Who is that girl?
She's my assistant.
They are done now.
- Come here and help me, come on!
- I'm coming!
Great! Thank you,
Mr. Pastry Chef.
Anyway, I have a question to ask:
What is this medicine
that I put in the pastries?
It's not poison, is it?
- Oh, no! Only Vitamin C.
- I don't believe it!
Hey, you! Why did you
say "I don't believe it"?
Do you know something
about these pastries?
Not me... I... I don't know
anything about this medicine.
These pastries are
really very good.
I see...! Then you will
eat these pastries...
...in which Vitamin C
has been put! Eat them!
Eat them! Eat them now!
Try eating them! Come on, eat them!
Eat them, come on! Come
on! I order you to eat them!
Get her! That girl
knows about the pastries!
Don't let her
escape! Go, quickly!
Yes!
Stop! Stop!
Opal, let's go!
- Stop! Stop!
- Stop!
Who ordered these
pastries from you?
Tell me! Who ordered
these pastries from you?
Fine! If you don't want to
tell me, it doesn't matter!
I'm taking them with me anyway!
And now go!
Mr. Pastry Chef, please
give me those pastries!
So you weren't a girl!
No, no! I will deliver them
to the man who ordered them from me!
I've decided to take them!
You'd better give them to me!
No, absolutely not!
I absolutely cannot give them to you!
- What happened?
- I couldn't get them, sir.
What do you mean?! Perhaps the pastry chef
hadn't made them yet?
What?!
Prince Sapphire came?!
Damn it! Ken!
Here I am, Mr. Nylon!
I don't want to hear anything more about Sapphire!
Go back there and this time
take the pastries!
Yes, sir!
And do whatever you want
with Prince Sapphire!
Let's go!
I've come to take those pastries!
Damn you!
You won't be able to stop me anyway!
I did it! I did it!
Well done!
And now deal with Sapphire!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I am the pastry chef! Don't shoot!
But why do you want to kill me?
I don't want you to tell
anyone anything about the pastries,
so, to silence you,
I will kill you.
Good heavens! Dirty cowards!
They tricked me!
I assure you that I didn't know
that that medicine was poisonous!
I didn't know! I only obeyed
by making those pastries.
And do you know who they want
to eat them?
As far as I know, they want
everyone at the castle to eat them:
the King, the Queen, the Prince...
In short, everyone!
Oh, my God!
I forgot something important:
they will be eaten during tea
this afternoon!
What?!
But tea time will be here soon!
Fortunately, there is still a
whole package of pastries left!
I'll try to get those men
out there to eat them.
That way, they will be
as obedient as that parrot!
Eat this!
Listen well, you who
have eaten my pastries!
Now there is no more
need for you to hunt me!
- Yes, sir!
- See?
The pastry medicine
has taken effect.
Fantastic!
Prince, we won't get in your way anymore!
Now you must tell me who it was
who ordered you to kill me!
I don't know his name.
I didn't even see him,
because he gave the order
to our leader.
Is there anyone who knows?
Prince, hurry up
and return to the castle!
- I'm going!
- And you, get out of here!
Never return to this forest again!
I order you!
- But at least are they good?
- They are delicious.
I had them made
by the best pastry chef in town.
Good! Now deliver them to the servants!
Make sure that everyone who
is close to Sapphire eats them.
Yes, sir.
I hope you have killed
the man who made them.
They are killing him now,
along with Sapphire.
What? Along with Sapphire?!
Are you sure they can manage
to kill him? Sapphire is strong!
I am absolutely sure they will!
Then I will carry out
a plan of mine.
Special troops! Special troops!
Duralumin orders you to kill
the King and his family!
The medicine calmed those wild
men in a second!
If Mom and Dad
take that horrible medicine,
they will be forever obedient
to Grand Duke Duralumin!
Your Majesty, it's tea time
Put everything on the table
and call the others.
We will have tea all together.
Yes, Your Majesty.
That's a tank!
Gunpowder arrows!
Get them, Opal! Get them!
Stop, or I will kill you!
Who gave you
the order to kill me?
We were ordered
by our Captain, sir!
Don't lie, soldier! It must have
been an order from Duralumin!
- I don't know!
- Opal!
Let the horse
go!
- You will return on foot.
- Very well, sir.
- Aren't they coming?
- They will arrive soon, Your Majesty
- In the meantime, eat.
- No, I will wait for them.
These pastries
look delicious.
- I apologize for the delay.
- Forgive me, Your Majesty.
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, you are always late.
Prince Sapphire has arrived!
Open the gates at once!
What are you doing?
Open immediately!
These pastries
look delicious.
- Don't you think?
- Yes.
I wonder if Sapphire will ever be
able to make ones just like them.
Prince Sapphire, one day,
will make even better ones!
Sapphire, what the hell is going on?!
Father, mother, forgive
me if I had to act this way.
- Those pastries were poisoned!
- Good heavens! Really?
What happened, Sapphire?
Tell me everything, please.
Right away.
But I cannot accuse anyone
of having ordered them,
because I lack the proof.
So, Nylon?
Sapphire has managed
to get on his side...
...our accomplices,
with the help of those pastries.
Idiot!
Maybe I overcooked them, but I'm
sure they must be delicious!
Not bad...
Really not bad!
You wouldn't tell
that it's the first time you've made them.
I'm glad
that they turned out well.
But it tastes bad! It's bitter!
Sapphire, you will manage to do
everything that girls do.
With a little effort,
you will learn to make...
...even the most delicious
sweets in the world.
Do you really believe
that I will learn to cook, father?
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP